Google released Gemini 3 Pro last week,
the most powerful AI model out there.
And alongside it, Nano Banana Pro, one
of, if not the best image generator and
editor out there. So, I decided to put
it to the test for generating product
photography and images for advertising
and marketing for ecom brands. In this
video, I'll run you through the entire
product photography system I have built
on NAN, including a live demo with
results, the backend NAN system, and the
lovable front end. You can get this
template in my premium school community,
the AI Avengers Lab down below. And if
you want to work with me to have this or
any other AI system built out for you,
book a discovery call with me down
below. Without further ado, let's get
right into it. So, this is the N system
and it starts with either a web hook,
which is the Lovable front-end UI. So,
if you're using Lovable, the images and
the data that you're going to upload as
the input will come through here. And
then there's also the alternative, the N
form submission. So this is the native n
form. So this is what you would use if
you're unfamiliar with lovable or if you
just prefer an easy setup without using
lovable. So anyways, I'll show you the
front-end UI. So if I go on here, you
can see that this is a lovable page that
I made. So I just made a quick landing
page and this is where I would upload my
image and I would select product
photography and then generate now and
then my results will come up here. So I
am creating a generation system with NAN
that will turn images into UGC content
and also a photo shoot for ecom brands.
So right now only product photography is
available. So in the upcoming days I'm
going to reveal the system to you. So
stay tuned for that. But for now only
product photography is available. So
I'll just quickly upload an image now.
So I've just uploaded a photo of a Tom
Ford tobacco oud fragrance. This is a
fragrance that I love to use. So I'm
going to choose this. And also you can
upload JPG, PNG or WEBP file types here.
And then I'm just going to select
product photography. And then I'm going
to click generate now. So while we wait
for this and then within the next 5
minutes it's going to load the images
here. But if it takes more than 5
minutes then it's going to time out and
we can view it on the air table back
end. But for now I'll just quickly
explain. So this will be appropriate for
making product images and photography of
things like fragrances, earrings,
jewelry, clothes, and other items. I
even tried a book and it works. So yeah,
you can generate product images of most
things here. And in the meantime, I'll
show you some images that it did
produce. This is the air table back end
where all my results are saved. The name
of the photo, so it's based on the
nature of the photo, like the vibe of
it, and then the prompt that was used on
the back end. So each prompt is
customized according to the image that
was uploaded. And then yeah, here are
the attachments. So this is the photo.
So I uploaded psychology of money and
this is how it turned out. And then I'll
show you another one. This is a Tom Ford
leather jacket. This is how it turned
out. Another photo of the psychology of
money. Here's another one. So while the
photos are really nice and cool, just
remember that if it has a lot of text in
it, then it might not get the text
correct. So, just remember that it's
only good for things like earrings or or
like simple accessories, jewelry, and
clothes. It's not the most consistent
when it comes to more intricate details
or having a lot of text, for example.
This is just a heads up for now. But
anyways, let's go back to the lovable
front end. So, it's still waiting for
the visuals to be created. This usually
takes around 3 to 5 minutes. Sometimes
it might take longer, but it usually
generates around eight images at a time.
So, let's just wait for this to finish.
So unfortunately it went over 5 minutes.
So it did not load here. However, the
execution was successful. As you can see
here, it succeeded in 5 minutes 46
seconds. And if I look on the air table
back end, you can see that it has
appeared over here. Let's take a look at
the results. So this is the first photo.
So let's wait for it to load. Here it
is. You can see that it looks very good.
And also the text is pretty accurate as
well. OD perform 50 mil. So it's not
perfect.
So, it's not 100% perfect, but it's very
close. However, the image is very
stunning and impressive. It's
levitating, which is really cool as
well. And like levitating, it might seem
strange, but you just know that it's
very welldesigned and a really cool
photo. So, let's go on to the next one
here.
Tobacco. And yes, this is very nice,
very sophisticated, very sexy, and I
absolutely love this design. So, yeah,
you can see the quality of the photos
that it can generate. So you can see the
power of Nano Banana Pro. You can see it
really shining. So let's go on to the
next one. Tobacco. So this is a little
bit bright. Maybe it's because of the
lighting, but anyways, it looks very
nice as well.
And let's go on to the next one here. So
this is a very chic, highass, dark,
mysterious image. I really like it as
well. You can definitely use this for
product photography and image on a ecom
store selling fragrances. So let's go on
to the next one. So these four was are
studio photos. So they're like the kind
of photos that you would expect to see
in a studio. And then there's one in the
environment, one out in the open. So
this one's up in the mountains. And
yeah, you can see that it looks very
nice. And let's just zoom in a little
bit. And yes, the text is very accurate.
Tobacco Odapform uh 50 mil. So this is
another very wealthy, highass image.
Kind of makes you think of yourself in
the Alps at your accommodation. So it
just makes you imagine yourself in the
Alps on a ski trip and this is like your
accommodation. So yeah, let's go on to
the next one. So that's extremely big
for 50 mil. So like this is definitely
not 50 mil, but it's still a very nice
setting. This looks like the Amalfi
Coast. It's not accurate. I would take
this out, but it's a very nice setting
nevertheless. It would have been nice.
If this was smaller, I would definitely
use it. But yeah, this just goes to show
that it's amazing, but it's not perfect.
So let's go on to the next one.
the seventh one. Okay. Yeah, it's a nice
setting like in a private jet, but yeah,
I would not use this. And then this is
the last one. Okay. Yep, I would take
this out. Nice setting, but yeah, I
would take this out because it got it
completely wrong. So, yeah, you can see
through the eight images that I showed
you that the setting and like the vibe
and the atmosphere that the photos
convey to you, it's really nice and
gives off that very sophisticated,
luxurious feel that the brand Tom Ford
has. And it's exactly what I would think
of when I would use my fragrance Tom for
tobacco hoot. But it just goes to show
that it's not 100% perfect, but when it
is, it's amazing. Out of these ones, I
would probably say either this one or
this one would be my favorite. You just
got to play around with it. But yeah,
that was just a quick demo. Now, I'm
going to go into the N workflow here and
how it works, and I'm going to walk you
through it. So, if you want this custom
built for you and tailored to you and
your specific business and needs, then
book a free discovery call with me down
below. And if you want to stay to
understand the NAN workflow and to learn
and be able to build your own system,
your own version of this, then stick
around till the end. And I also have
this template in my premium school
community, the AI Avengers Lab down
below. Go check that out if you want
this template. But anyways, I'll just
get right into it. First, it's going to
take in the input. So like the photo
that you select through the web hook
here, the lovable web hook or on the NN
form. Let's just go on to the NN form
and then yeah just describe your form
title description and then image select
file for element type. You can have
multiple files if you like and accept
these file types. So JPG, PNG, WEBP,
JPEG and they have to be required fields
as well. Respond when form is submitted
and then you would have this um HTTP
request here. So how it works is now you
use an HTTP request to upload the image
onto cloudinary. So get method and URL
here and also you have to send a body
under the body that you're going to
send. You have to put name upload preset
and that's your username and then API
key and then your API key here. So these
are all placeholders and then you would
put file here for the next one and then
you would put image underscore. So this
will be the same if you use the same
type of form that I have. So this is for
n form and if you upload it to lovable
it's basically the same thing except
this will be different. So file and then
data zero. It's just like the name of
the file when it's uploaded onto n once
n receives it. It's going to be
different. So if it's done with the
lovable front end it's going to be data
zero. Otherwise it's going to be image
and then you're going to ask openai to
analyze the image for you. So this is
the prompt here. I'm not going to go
over the whole thing. Basically just a
quick rundown. So your role. So you're a
product analysis extractor reverse
engineers product photography. You're
going to generate structured metadata.
So this is the main goal of this node
and your task is to analyze the image
and a product analysis JSON object that
captures the product identification,
physical attributes, brand positioning
and then the emotional intent based on
the styling and the context. And also
you can use any kind of photo. So if you
took photo of a fragrance in your hand
and you upload that, then that will
work. Or you could just use regular
product images with a blank background,
that can work as well. That tends to
work better. But yeah, you can use any
kind of image as long as the subject
product is clear on the photo. Analysis
priority. These are the things that it
needs to prioritize when it analyzes it.
Colors, materials, the shape, the label,
and the branding. So break down any text
and anything related to like brand
labeling. And then deduce like the
context. So if it's the Tom Ford
fragrance for example,
then you can see that it's a dark
fragrance and it looks sophisticated and
then it's going to infer that and then
it's going to look up what Tom Ford is.
Well, it knows what Tom Ford is and then
it's going to relate the two together.
And yeah, this is conservative unknown.
This is just kind of like a fallback
mechanism. So in case that it doesn't
understand what brand it is, if it sees
a Nike tick, then it's going to know
that it's Nike and that it's going to be
related to fitness and athleticism. But
yeah, this is just like a fallback
mechanism. And then you're going to
provide all the different image
categories here. So I'm not going to
read all of it, but anyways, like
bottles, equipment, kitchen, lighting,
interior use, fitness equipment,
resistance bands, jewelry, watches,
bags. So yeah, everything here like you
can add to this category, but yeah, just
like define all the different categories
that you like that you're going to
intend to use it for and the logic here.
So this is just to help the AI identify
what kind of product it is. This is
another guide to help the AI identify
what kind of product it is and like the
kind of like vibe and image that it
gives off. So like luxury, you can
define it with like marble surfaces,
gold accents, and casual is like
everyday settings like relaxed,
approachable styling. So just like
t-shirt, jeans, and target emotion
inference rules like calm, muted tones.
It gives you the mood of tranquility and
peace, dramatic, and bold. So that's
going to show like a bit of power,
ambition. So if you see like a navy
double breasted suit, then you're going
to know that it's associated with power
and style and success and status, right?
So like Wall Street powers suits. So
yeah, like these are all guides that's
going to help the AI identify what kind
of product it is. So you have to add all
the logic that you can think of. So you
can add all the logic that you like
that's going to help the AI identify
what kind of product this is. and then
like physical attributes material like
the finish distinct distinctive features
and then here is like the JSON schema as
well. So you have to define the JSON
schema. So like product name, brand
category, subcategory, physical
attributes and under physical attributes
like color, material, finish, form
factor, I could go on and on.
Distinctive features, brand positioning,
target emotion, used context. So yeah, I
try to be as comprehensive as I can
while adding only things that were
necessary, but if you want to add more,
then feel free to do so. But yeah, make
sure to clearly define the JSON that
you'll be using for the rest of the
workflow. So yeah, there's the rest of
the prompts. So edge case handling. So
this is important as well. So make sure
that it's able to handle edge cases,
otherwise it's not going to be
production ready like voice AI, AI
agents, anything like that. In order to
be production ready, it has to be able
to handle edge cases and scenarios that
you necessarily wouldn't have predicted.
And also list the common mistakes to
avoid so the AI knows what kind of
mistakes that it needs to avoid making
and how to do it properly as well
because if you want to do something
properly, you not only have to know how
to do it, but you also have to know what
not to do. Anyways, that's like the
prompt is very comprehensive. I didn't
go over the whole thing, but I did as
much as I could. So, I hope that helped.
Anyways, let's go on to the next bit.
Edit fields. So, here I just defined the
prompt again for the next step. I just
decided to do the prompt in here. So
this prompt here, it basically uses chat
GBT to create a new prompt for me to
generate the best possible images. I'm
going to go over this very briefly, but
yeah, you are universal product
photography prompt generator. Your task
is to generate a category agnostic JSON
uh photography prompts. So we will be
using JSON prompting. So, if you don't
know what JSON prompting is, so JSON
prompting is basically just a prompt
where you instead of just you typing um
create a marketing plan for a men's suit
brand. So, instead of just writing out a
prompt like that, you're basically
organizing and categorizing the entire
prompt into a JSON here. So, like
Jason's, they are very well organized.
It modulates everything. So under
realism anchor for example it's going to
describe the level of realism and under
creative strategy it's going to describe
like the primary pillars the
psychological triggers the viral
elements and emotional journey what kind
of impression that it gives to people.
So it categorizes everything in a JSON.
So a JSON categorizes everything. So
yeah basically this prompt it generates
a JSON prompt for you. So I've already
went over these bits. So like defining
the category. So I won't be reading them
one by one but anyways let's go to the
JSON schema. So realism anchors creative
strategy the subject. You can see that
I'm being very comprehensive here of the
type details styling physical attributes
product integration product name
placement interactions. So you can see
that I'm defining the JSON for every
single possible image that I could
upload here. So while the Tom Ford
fragrance that I uploaded, it doesn't
have like a human hand or like any kind
of interaction within the image, you can
see that I've accounted for it by for
example, if I am holding it with my hand
or if I'm spraying it on myself, then
it's going to take it that into account.
And then you have to have a setting part
as well. So Jason and then the props,
the lighting. So lighting is extremely
important. You have to have this one and
camera film stock like technical detail.
So like the aspect ratio, the style
notes, the color palette, color
psychology, composition strategy,
storytelling elements. So this is
exactly why it was able to create the
Tom Ford fragrance in the hotel at the
Alps and then style tags, mood keywords.
So you can see that I'm being very
comprehensive here. If you're already
confused about what's going on, then
yeah, don't worry. This confused me a
lot at first. But yeah, make your life
easier. Just use chat GPT or claw to
define the JSON for you. So in your
prompt, always have a section where you
verify your final output and have kind
of like a checklist. So it goes through
this and verifies it before providing an
output. And yeah, it would be nice to
provide an example as well just so the
AI understands what to do better. So
like for example, product name, AirPods
Pro, U Apple Tech, wireless earbuds,
etc. and scene description. So yeah,
that's it for this prompt. And then what
we are going to do is we are going to
insert it in here. And then this is
where the magic happens. So we're taking
the image that we uploaded and we are
using the JSON prompt that we created
and we are using that JSON prompt to
create the product images and then it's
going to make the request on foul here.
So if you don't know what foul is, foul
is where you can make API requests to
make images or videos. So this is foul
over here. So you can explore all the
different um video and image models. So
you can see that there's nano banana,
cadream, the Chinese one, bo 3.1, sore
2. So you can use all of these with API
requests here. So just create a foul AI
account and then get your API key. So
what you want to do uh once you create a
file account, you want to go under
manage and then you want to go under um
API keys and then create your API key
here and then copy that into n. So here
I'm using authentication generic
credential type. Select header O and
then once you have header O then you
just want to create a new header O
credential add authorization and then
copy and paste your API key into here
and then just use that
and then since this one is actually
making a request to file to create the
actual image with nano banana just paste
the JSON output here.
So here we're just making the request
and over here we're just making sure
that the request has been made and then
what's going to happen is you're going
to make a request to file AI to create
the images and then you are going to
create a new prompt here. So this new
prompt it's going to generate eight
different prompts with different
artistic styles and directions. So ro
task inputs you can see that it's
clearly been defined for you. So it's
going to take the product image, the
category and the keywords. And then it's
going to create the style and the
prompt.
So you can see that it's been clearly
defined here. So the technicals, the
process, the output. So the JSON output
and then the rules example prompt style.
So this is a prompt that f is going to
use to generate the images. And then
we're going back here. This is going to
generate the eight different prompts
that's going to allow the creation of
the eight different product images. And
then first we are going to save the
prompts and the name into air table. So
I have an air table base where I am
saving the name of that image and also
the prompt. So this is the air table
here. I'm just using air table instead
of Google sheets because I can actually
see the image on an air table sheet. So
the name the prompt. So studio volutric
neon and then the prompt just paste it
here to understand what prompt that it
followed and then the status. So once
it's done it's done. and then the
attachment here and then the output
here. So just copy this air table. So
name, prompt, status, attachment and
then let's go back. Once we add the data
into the air table, then we're going to
loop around each of the eight image
styles that we're going to create. And
then we are going to make the request
and then we're going to check if the
image has been completed or not. And if
it hasn't then it's going to go back and
it's going to loop around until it's
finished. And once it's finished, then
it's going to add the output to air
table. And then it's going to loop over
again and finish off the other images
that it has remaining. And if it's
failed, then it's going to update failed
here. That could happen if you're out of
credits and you don't have auto recharge
or if your card failed or some other
technical issue. But anyways, if it
fails, then it's just going to say
failed and then it's going to loop
around again until all eight are
finished. And once all eight are
finished, you're going to send a web
hook response. So this is going to tell
Lovable that the images have been
generated and it would be loaded here.
So if it times out but just now it took
over 5 minutes so it didn't load. But
yeah, this is just a response to show
that it has been completed. It's quite
simple. JSON JSON data and then
application JSON. So I didn't go over
most of this because you can go over it
in your own time. So yeah, you will have
access to this template in my school
community. So you can take it, you can
modify it, you can reverse engineer, you
can learn from it, you can do whatever
you like. But anyways, that was just a
quick but somewhat detailed rundown of
the NAN system. If I went into every
single node, then it would probably take
like over an hour to go through this
whole system. But I hope that it helped
you understand the workflow better. And
one last thing, I'll go over what I did
on Lovable to create this landing page
over here. So, let's go on to Lovable.
So, here I have defined the prompt. You
are a world-class web designer and blah
blah blah flattering the AI telling it
that it's amazing, which it is. So yeah,
design a modern landing page and then
what you have to do is you have to take
the web hook link and then you have to
paste it here. So what you would have to
do is you would have to go back to the
workflow here, go on to your web hook
and then go on to production URL. You
would copy this and then you would paste
it into here. So tell it that when the
user uploads your image and selects an
option, the site will send the file and
their selection via post request to the
webbook that you will paste here. And
then yeah, you can just define the
design. So like moistic like the font
animations
and then the page layout. This is mostly
just design just like do whatever you
like with the design. But yeah, what you
have to do is you need this part here
defining the web hook. But yeah, that
wasn't the only prompt that I put into
lovable. So I'll just like quickly go
over the rest of it. And you also have
to tell it that it's going to respond to
the web hook and that you have to
display the images here once it's done
uploading. And you also have to define
what kind of file types that you can
upload here. So JPEG, PNG, WEBP, choose
your style, product photography. So like
if you're going to do all three, which
you know I will be doing, then yeah, you
can do that. Otherwise, you could
probably skip this and then have a
button to generate now. And you have to
tell it to send this payload into your N
web hook link and then have N respond to
the web hook, send back the finished
images, and display them over here. So
yeah, that's basically it. just the
design, just the layout and how it's
going to work where you can see the
results and the design of course. So the
design I'll just let you play around
with it and also set up the air table
here in case it times out and you don't
see the images here or if it doesn't
work. Otherwise, you can just use the n
form over here at the beginning of the
workflow. So yeah, that was it for this
video. I hope you found this video
useful and helpful. And if you did,
please leave a like and subscribe. So if
you want access to this full system then
join AI Avengers lab down below. And if
you want this exact system built out for
you or any kind of AI automation system
or any kind of AI agent built out for
you then book a discovery call with me
down below. So once again, thanks for
watching and I'll see you in the next